[
  {
    "question": "What is the general subject of the book?",
    "answer": "The making of armor and the regulations that controlled the armourer and his craft from the 11th to the 16th century."
  },
  {
    "question": "Besides the history of armour, what records are discussed in the book?",
    "answer": "Records and references in English documents relating to the actual making of armour and the regulations which controlled the Armourer and his Craft."
  },
  {
    "question": "What offensive weapon is intentionally omitted from the book's discussion?",
    "answer": "The sword."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is included in the book, that has been practically overlooked by all English writers?",
    "answer": "A polyglot glossary."
  },
  {
    "question": "Name one of the continental writers that have added greatly to our store of information on the subject of armourers",
    "answer": "Dr. Wendelin Boeheim, Gurlitt, Buff, or Angellucci."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the book identify as a standard work on helmets and mail?",
    "answer": "The Catalogue of Helmets and Mail compiled by Baron de Cosson and the late J. Burges."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the period covered in the book?",
    "answer": "From the 11th to the 16th century."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the book discuss besides the making of armour?",
    "answer": "Regulations controlling the armourer and his craft."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the book contain regarding armour and weapons?",
    "answer": "A polyglot glossary of words dealing with armour and weapons."
  },
  {
    "question": "What city's Armourers' Company is mentioned in the book?",
    "answer": "The Armourersâ€™ Company of the City of London."
  },
    {
    "question": "What are some of the topics covered relating to the craft of the armourer?",
    "answer": "Tools, appliances, iron, steel, proofing, decoration and cleaning."
  },
  {
    "question": "What materials other than metal were used in conjunction with armour?",
    "answer": "Fabrics, linen, and leather."
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspects of wearing armour are discussed?",
    "answer": "How armour was worn."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the processes mentioned in making armour?",
    "answer": "Plating."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the book dedicated to?",
    "answer": "The Right Honourable The Viscount Dillon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the types of illustrations included in the book?",
    "answer": "Diagrams and plates"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the components of armour discussed?",
    "answer": "Pauldrons and Sollerets."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the features that armour can have?",
    "answer": "glancing surfaces"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a 'passguard'?",
    "answer": "A reinforcing piece for the joust"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a 'mainfaire'?",
    "answer": "A gauntlet (main de fer)"
  },
    {
    "question": "What kind of armour was used for horses?",
    "answer": "Cuissard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for the master armourer?",
    "answer": "Harnischmeister"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the components of horse armour?",
    "answer": "Cuissard"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where were armourers' guilds located?",
    "answer": "Florence."
  },
  {
    "question": "How was armour attached to the body?",
    "answer": "By points"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was used for padding under armour?",
    "answer": "Harnische-kappe"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was mail made of?",
    "answer": "Linked rings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the jack?",
    "answer": "A coat worn by foot-soldiers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a brigandine?",
    "answer": "A type of armour"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Stechzeug?",
    "answer": "A type of armour"
  }
]
